We'll be right back.
Hey, stop jumping around!
We're getting nowhere!
I was hoping my four powers would be enough, but I guess not.
I'm afraid I haven't mastered the finger pistols yet, but I've got a little stand-in that should do the job quite nicely.
All right, this is my chance to go to the next car!
Hey, I thought we were having a fight here!
He thinks he's smart.
I got you now.
Nice try, but I saw that coming from a mile away!
You son of a bitch!
Ouchie finger!
This ain't good.
It's got my number now.
Take this!
Just grazed me!
Sure moves around a lot, though.
I know your weak point.
It's your back, isn't it?
And that's not counting your brain, which is an obvious weakness, too.
At this rate, it's only a matter of time before you're finished.
Don't get ahead of yourself, pal.
I got a move that'll get rid of my weak point easy.
Frankie!
Invincible!
Eat that!
Now do you give up, weasel face?
Yes.
That's so stupid, I don't even have a comeback.
What's going on?
How did you get here in the first place?
This is dangerous, you know.
Ma'am, I can hardly answer if you bombard me with questions like that.
Let's just calm down and take it slowly.
Ah, shall I pour you some coffee, perhaps?
Stop fooling around!
What are you...
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Sniper King, the King of the Snipers.
To make a long story short, I've come to rescue you.
You're really serious.
I'm not alone, of course.
Your friend Sanji and a cyborg thug named Frankie
are currently engaged in battle on this train.
They kept the enemy busy long enough for me to come here.
Furthermore, Captain Luffy and the rest of the Straw Hats
are following closely on another sea train.
I hear he's bringing a small army with him.
On my way here, I peeked inside the other train cars.
Frankly, I believe the four agents in the car behind us
may prove too great a challenge.
If possible, I would like to escape with you
before Sanji has to face them.
Come, let's run away.
Together!
What's the matter?
There's no need to worry.
I've made all of the necessary preparations.
Here.
These octo-shoes are for you.
If you use them on your hands and feet,
you can climb through the window
and stick to the outer panels of the sea train.
Quickly, put them on before they notice.
I won't go.
Why not?
I don't know why you're doing this.
I told you very clearly that I wouldn't see you again.
I said that I would never return to the Straw Hats.
The situation has changed.
They know why you turned yourself in.
That ice gentleman from the shipyard clarified everything.
So he survived after all?
But still, that doesn't change my mind.
I won't go with you no matter what.
Enough with that already.
Don't you get it?
They aren't so weak that they need you to worry about them.
What were you thinking?
Accepting such a stupid deal
before talking to the rest of the crew.
You think they'd be happy to go on?
Knowing that one of their friends
had thrown her life away for them?
Now that they know why you left,
they'll follow you to the depths of hell if they have to.
And they'll bust every skull they can on the way there.
You don't get it, do you?
That's the kind of guy Luffy is.
How many times do I have to tell you this?
Even if you think you can save me,
I don't want your help.
Don't you care how I feel?
Come on, give me a break.
Hey, keep it down in there, you.
What's the matter?
Now that we're getting close to Eni's lobby,
is that cool exterior of yours
finally starting to melt away?
Well, you can cry all you like,
but there's no point in lamenting your fate
after it's already been sealed.
Really, I'm fine.
Strange.
That's not the reaction I was expecting.
I can't put my finger on it,
but there's something different about her.
Maybe it's just my imagination?
I said I'm fine.
Now please, just leave me alone.
This is definitely fishy.
Why is she goofing off at a time like this?
Rabbit ears?
Kai, would you take this seriously?
You can't just quit because you are losing.
Get up and fight me.
I'll spit on you.
I'd watch my weasel mouth if I were you, punk.
I'm not quitting.
I'm just getting started.
Anyway, this is nothing but bad luck.
Well, bad luck for you, I mean.
I'm doing great.
Did I mention I was super this week?
It's not a good time to make me angry.
Let me ask you something, brother.
Have you ever heard of a creature they call a centaur?
Huh?
You mean those things that are human from the waist up
and like a horse from the waist down?
Yeah, what about them?
Convert!
No way.
That's ridiculous.
Frankie!
Centaur Mo!
It's backwards!
Your head's supposed to be in the front, not your crotch!
You call this backwards?
Just wait till I rearrange your face, weasel boy.
Are we there yet?
Where's Bash and Tom?
It's huffing Tom!
Anyway, get inside before you catch a cold.
You just changed clothes and you're soaking wet already.
I don't care, it's more awesome up here!
Fine.
Now, gum gum!
300 caliber cannon!
Boom!
Whoa!
Yeah!
We got a family!
Would all of you stop screwing around?
We're bored.
Then polish your weapons or something.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, I tried to tell those guys the same thing earlier, but they wouldn't listen to me.
Hey, check it out!
There's a train in front of us!
It's the puffing Tom!
Seems a bit early, don't you think?
Who's in my armpit?
I can't move!
Damn it.
What's going to happen to us now?
There's no engine on this car.
All we can do is wait it out.
Another way!
Oh, this storm is still pretty bad.
You think someone will come save us?
We're in big trouble if they don't.
Hey, guys!
There's something approaching from behind!
Really?
It must be a rescue ship.
I don't think so.
Actually, it looks like it's coming on the railway.
There's no way.
There's only one sea train in the world and we're on it right now.
Besides, it's Aqua Laguna.
No one could make it out of Water 7 in this weather.
Well, if it's not a train, then...
What the heck is it?
That's the puffing Tom, all right.
But it's just a caboose.
There's no engine.
And it doesn't look like it's moving.
That can't be right.
What's going on here?
Does this mean it got detached somehow?
Maybe something happened and Sanji and Usopp are on there.
Big bro Frankie, too.
Well, I hope not, because we're about to crash into them.
Frankie, hit the brake!
I already told you now, didn't I?
We don't got one.
We're going to crash!
Luffy, what are you going to do?
I'm flying over to see what's up.
Now come, go!
Rockets!
Whoa!
There's something in the sky!
What happened?
Ow, ow, ow!
All right!
I made it!
Who the hell is this weirdo?
Hello?
Saji, are you in here?
Poor Usopp.
Hey, Saji!
You hear me?
Maybe over there.
Wait a sec, I know that face!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Hello?
Are you there?
Saji!
Shut up!
I can't hear!
Bring it on!
We're not scared of you!
Where's Saji?
Wait, what?
I don't know who that is.
Saji!
He's my friend!
Sorry, never heard of him.
Too bad.
See ya!
Shoot him!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Get up!
Straw Hat's coming out!
Looks like they're shooting him, and he's saying no!
Well, whatever happened, the train cars must be full of marines.
So, what's the plan, rope man?
If we don't move those cars out of the way, we might get knocked off!
Guess I liked that one
That's why there's one light
I've been seen
If I follow you
All right, run away
I won't be straight
I've given you
... always
... attend
Who the hell is that?
Ah! That's the Ship Slasher!
Ship Slasher?
Ship Slasher T-Bone! A captain from Navy Headquarters!
He uses a straight sword to cut through ships like a raw steak!
Sounds like fun.
Hey, Steak Man, draw your sword or get out of the way!
On the next, One Piece, Clash!
Demon Slasher Zorro vs. Ship Slasher T-Bone!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!